Hello to all of you, in this section I am going to tell you
how to fill the Central KYC form, so first of all,
take the Central KYC form from the company for which you want to fill it
or you can also download it on Google Chrome, you can
easily download it on Google Chrome, so
after downloading it on Google Chrome, you will get the form like this, so this
line which is above, this
part, you have to fill the office of this
club, complete it, this is the
form below, how is it made, then do it
below, to fill the form, first of all
you tick it, after that do the name matching,
after correcting them, show you the
fee, it means Mr. Message
or Miss, isn't it, my name is
written as Mukesh Kumar Sinha on the Aadhar card, so I will write
Mukesh here, I will write Kumar here
and I will write Sinha here and
if suppose it is written as Mukesh Sinha, then I will
write Mr. here, I will
write Mukesh here and I am playing a little,
okay, after this I will directly meet the last one and
write Siddh, okay  Suppose there is a woman, then you will
write the woman's name here,
after that write the first name, middle name and
last name, after that
you will write your name before marriage here,
okay in this section,
write your name before marriage, after that your father's name,
put Mr in Father's name,
after that take the first name, middle name, last name,
this is your father's
name Suresh Kumar Sinha, so what will you put
Surya here, here you will put Kumari and
put it here, okay let's go ahead, mother and
mother's name, so here is the middle, after that if the
owner and your mother's name is Gauri symbol,
then write Gauri here, take
Siddha here, this Gauri Devi will go here,
here divine will go and Sinha will go,
okay,
yes son, whatever date of birth
you have, fill the date, uniform, eye month and here,
fill it properly, if it is male
-female or transgender in gender, then
tick on 'I', okay, now after that
fill in the PAN number which is your PAN number, account number, in that form,
after that your form comes  If it is 16430 function then it is fine,
otherwise leave it,
after that comes proof of identity and
address and entry means identity card or
after that addition, if you find out if the address is Kamruddin,
then click on it,
after clicking it if it is a passport then
after clicking it you will do it, otherwise
leave it, if you do not want to correct it if it is a voter ID then
correct it, if you want to correct it then
give the number, if it is driving lessons then correct it
and fill its number, okay,
after that if it is not correct then leave it,
after that in audition it is fine, otherwise
leave it, after that come straight
down, offline verification based,
here you have to fill the Aadhar number, fill the Aadhar number, it is
required only after filling the Aadhar number
and see here, if you are okay then here
you have to put the photo and sign just after the photo,
whatever your signature will be,
you have to send it, you will
add ghee in it, it will be
written in the Aadhar card here because you have to
enter the Aadhar card, whatever will be written in the Aadhar card, in
which now you have to add the address,
you have to write its complete
address  I will write it as I write it in Aadhar card,
okay, you will write town, city,
district, we will write postal code, which is
your postal code, we will enter it, after this,
see here the state code, it is a little
visible thing, what will we do with it, let's see
both these, state and country code, so for
state code, let's go down one below,
let's vote for it, okay, so
further down,
here we see the state code,
you are seeing it in Chhattisgarh, so for
Chhattisgarh, you are seeing the code
CG, okay, then we will give the serial there,
after that the country code will come, in the country code
we have India, so look,
you are seeing the
A.I.N.D.I.N.I., see,
in this line, circle it, come
back and fill it here, if
your current address and I both are same, then we will
mash it up from here, if
not, then you will enter it here again and whatever you want to
enter, you will enter it here,
enter it in this line and
mention it here, whatever Aadhar number it is or
which you want to enter on the current side,
you have to mention it here
Whatever you want to enter, now add it to this group, enter
whatever you
want to enter and tick it,
okay, dial the number of animals here,
okay, the person is going and looking at it, if the
contact details are visible then
click here in contact details, if it is
mobile telephone number then it is fine,
otherwise leave it blank,
click here, note down the mobile number here
because it is the code of India, run the app on it, you will
give the mobile number, enter the email ID,
after that leave the plane blank,
leave it blank,
after that the dates are visible here, so the
date has to be entered of the date on which you are filling it
and the Mandal is filled in the
name of that place, okay, then
sign here, okay, after that what is below,
it is of no use to us, it will be
filled by the office people, okay, in this way
your form is complete, after
completing the form, attaching the photo and signing it, you will attach
10 copies of proof, PAN number and
Aadhar card, which is quite clear,
you will register the form simply like this by demolishing your concerned office  If you
like the video, please like, share
and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you.